<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="update_text">"v3.5.2:
 - fix for SGS2 on Android 4.0.4
 - minor fixes and improvements
 

 v3.5.1:
 - fix for not discovered interfaces for MANY devices. To use that fix if you are affected you have to REINSTALL.
 

 v3.5.0:
 - fixed that connection fee is calculated at free times and free numbers
 - connection fee now works with calltime limit together
 - added a new network interfaces (also Motorola Razr)
 - small and internal improvements
 

 v3.4.2:
 - new czech language integrated
 - renewed polish language
 

 v3.4.0:
 - you can add basic fees (for example for the cost limits)
 - you can add call startup costs
 - you can split SMS on 80 chars
 - nicer widget dialog
 - added hungarian translation
 - hardware acceleration for Android Honeycomb
 - bugfixes
 

 v3.3.3:
 - visible for honeycomb tablets in Android Market (but no adjusted UI)
 - fix for a wrong interface detection leading to \"hanging\" data usage counters
 

 v3.3.2:
 - small fixes
 

 v3.3.1:
 - small fix for greek and polish version
 

 v3.3.0:
 - added minutes/sms exchange (unit limit)
 - added support for newer samungs devices and firmwares
 - added another Wifi interface
 - added SMS polling. This is more reliable, but does not give Just-in-time updating of SMS (for widgets and notifications). Default is 90 minutes. Raise that value if you don't send much SMS. The old Just-in-Time updating did not work well on some firmwares, probably because it is not an offical API.
 - added possibility to enable sms and call costs independently
 - added possibility to enable different notifications independently
 - added interface reset option for people with data usage counting problems
 - improved swipe and tab-switching performance
 - added thumbs visualization of estimation
 - added polish translation
 - greek translation refreshed
 - fixed a exception
 

 v3.2.2:
 - added cost limit
 - added cost estimation
 - added data counting support for LG Optimus 2X
 - performance fixes
 - added danish translation
 

 v3.2.1:
 - added spanish translation
 - added a bugfix
 

 v3.2.0:
 - performance tweaks
 - some new icons
 - other widget caching (now they should have much better updating)
 - added 3600/3600 and 60/15 timing
 

 v3.1.3:
 - minor and major bugfixes
 

 v3.1.2:
 - bugfix for Android 1.6 devices
 

 v3.1.1:
 - added russian translation
 

 v3.1.0:
 - discover more devices and also future ones (hopefully). If nothing is detected, please clear you DroidStat data in the system app settings.
 - possibility to show hours and minutes (not only minutes)
 - two new average stats about call and sms length
 - some performance tweeks
 

 v3.0.4:
 - added possibility to select update interval for data usage counting
 - added manual correction for the stats
 - should support Samsungs Intercept data usage counting (needs reinstall)
 - should support Sony Ericsson Xperia X10i (another version) data usage counting (needs reinstall)
 - should support Samsung Captivate (another version) data usage counting (needs reinstall)
 

 v3.0.3:
 - added a fix for excluded numbers on some devices where patterns didn't match
 - ability to exclude numbers with patterns who aren't in contacts
 - should support Motorola Droid 2 data usage counting (needs reinstall)
 - should support Sony Ericsson Xperia X10i (another version) data usage counting (needs reinstall)
 - fixed support for Samsung Galaxy Tab data usage counting (needs reinstall, sorry ;-) )
 

 v3.0.2:
 - added greek translation
 - added chinese translation
 

 v3.0.1:
 - fixed crashing settings bug on 1.6 devices 
 - many new devices supported for data usage tracking (needs reinstall): 
 - HTC Liberty/Aria supported
 - HTC Desire HD supported
 - HTC HD2 supported
 - Samsung Captivate supported
 - Samsung Galaxy Tab supported
 - Motorola Milestone 2 supported
 

 v3.0.0:
 - incoming calls and sms usage tracking 
 - list performance tweek 
 - new fancy non-modal \"analyse\"-dialog
 - new Overview screen :-D
 - new stat favorites system
 

 v2.2.6:
 - different color levels for widget progressbar 
 - should support Samsung GT-I9000B and Samsung Vibrant (GT-I5500B) data usage counting (needs reinstall) 
 - fix for switched upload and download stats from last version
 - fixed bug not displaying tabs in QVGA Devices
 - widget supported under Android 1.5 again
 

 v2.2.5:
 - should support Droid X data usage counting (needs reinstall) 
 - internal code changes
 

 v2.2.4:
 - widget transparency not available any more (will come later). Widgetbugs hopefully fixed.
 - added 4 stats about average usage of calls and messages
 - WidgetInfo dialog which shows what is displayed on each widget
 - more QuickInfos boxes to help understanding all options
 - should support LG GT540 and Sony Ericsson X10i data usage counting (needs reinstall)
 

 v2.2.3:
 - 2x1 widget bug fixed
 

 v2.2.2:
 - faster analyze
 - number cleanup (more precise per-number counting and number-filtering) 
 - country code correction (more precise per-number counting and number-filtering) 
 - nicer info dialogs 
 - fixed an 'free hours &amp; days' bug which brought a FC 
 

 v2.2.1:
 - fixed critical bug
 

 v2.2.0:
 - added \"Force English\"-Button for other languages
 - should support WIFI stats for HTC Desire, HTC Wildfire and HTC Evo now (needs reinstall)
 - \"exclude free days and hours\"-feature added (restricted to no overlapping in free periods ATM)
 - data stats view improved
 - now it is able to select datalimits like 1500 MB
 

 v2.1.3:
 - added german translation
 

 v2.1.2:
 - support all currencies
 - fixed \"hanging sync\"-bug
 

 v2.1.1:
 - support 2 new Samsung devices
 - fixed progress bar bug with high limits
 - some little improvements
 

 v2.1.0:
 - complete data traffic integration
 (Please pay attention, this feature is BETA at the moment. Provide me with bugreports per email please)
 - 3x1 widget with data traffic
 - use cost option with limits switched off"</string>
    <string name="update_text_premium">"v3.5.3:
 - statusbar-widget works again
 

 v3.5.2:
 - added remaining days stat for the widgets
 - preparations for future feature
 

 v3.4.2:
 - added pie charts (Top Charts) for a lot of call and sms stats
 

 v3.4.0:
 - 2 new statistics for widgets selectable (billed sms sent month/total)
 - widget click is now dynamic to content of widget for all stats and widgets
 - different icons for cost stats to distinguish between them
 - backup and restore of configuration
 - import and export of Call and SMS events
 - export of all Call and SMS event in readable CSV format
 

 v3.3.0:
 - added event log (BETA-feature)
 - added homescreen shortcut for event-log
 - 7 new stats selectable in widgets
 

 v3.2.1:
 - added homescreen shortcut to data-per-app activity
 

 v3.2.0:
 - data-per-app feature (Froyo upwards phones)
 - fixed second statusbar widget slot
 

 v3.1.3:
 - added One-Slot 1x1 widget
 - extended Top3 list to Top10 list
 - added status bar widget
 

 v3.1.1:
 - added 4x1 widget
 

 v3.1.0:
 - total costs stat for widgets
 

 v3.0.4:
 - initial release
 - widgets value configurable
 - widgets without units possible
 - setting widget transparency possible
"</string>
    <string name="nitro_valueseekbar_set">Set</string>
    <string name="nitro_valueseekbar_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="unit_remaining_days">days</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_free">Free</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_premium">Premium</string>
    <string name="pro_widget_title">Widgets</string>
    <string name="pro_widget_txt">"Use the status bar widget as well as the extra large 4x1 widgets and the alternative 1x1 widget.
Choose any stat you want to display on the widgets
Define the transparency of the widgets"</string>
    <string name="pro_topstats_title">TopStats</string>
    <string name="pro_topstats_text">"Get the top 10 instead of only the top 3!
See a pie chart for every TopStat"</string>
    <string name="pro_eventlog_title">EventLog</string>
    <string name="pro_eventlog_text">Get the EventLog containing every phone call and text in chronological order and see how long you phoned and how much actually was billed</string>
    <string name="pro_dataperapp_title">DataPerApp</string>
    <string name="pro_dataperapp_text">See how much data each app used to find apps eating all your free data.</string>
    <string name="pro_gopremium_title">GoPremium</string>
    <string name="pro_gopremium_text">"To get the premium features all you need to do is install the premium key through one of the links provided below.
All your settings and stats will be preserved. The premium features will be available the next time you start the app."</string>
    <string name="premium_android_market">Android Market</string>
    <string name="premium_paypal">PayPal (2,50 €)</string>
    <string name="topstats_free_button_more">more</string>
    <string name="quickinfo_event_log">This log shows you all SMS and Call events which DroidStats gathered from your phone. These events are the base for the analysis. Click on each entry to get more info.</string>
    <string name="price_connection_fee">connection fee (per call)</string>
    <string name="use_connection_fee">use connection fee</string>
    <string name="use_basic_fee">use basic fee</string>
    <string name="price_basic_fee">basic fee (per month)</string>
    <string name="pref_export_config">Export Config</string>
    <string name="pref_export_data">Export Data</string>
    <string name="pref_import_config">Import Config</string>
    <string name="pref_import_data">Import Data</string>
    <string name="pref_export_csv">Export Event Log (CSV)</string>
    <string name="pref_export_config_sum">Backups configuration options to SD card including excluded numbers and times</string>
    <string name="pref_export_data_sum">Backups Call and SMS event data on SD card</string>
    <string name="pref_import_config_sum">Restores configuration from SD card (latest)</string>
    <string name="pref_import_data_sum">Restores Call and SMS event data from SD card and merges with current data (latest)</string>
    <string name="pref_export_csv_sum">Export your Call and SMS event data to readable CSV file</string>
    <string name="pref_use_unicode_sms_split">Split on 80 chars (Unicode)</string>
    <string name="pref_use_unicode_sms_split_sum">Check this if your messages gets splitted after 80 characters. This for some languages with special characters.</string>
    <string name="pref_importexport">Import/Export (BETA)</string>
    <string name="units_category">SMS/Minute Exchange</string>
    <string name="unit_limit_box_or">or</string>
    <string name="pref_gui">UI settings</string>
    <string name="pref_notifications_cat">Notification Settings</string>
    <string name="pref_unit_limit">Unit Limit (SMS/Minute exchange)</string>
    <string name="pref_unit_limit_sum">Activate this if you can exchange sms against minutes and vice versa. For example 100 minutes OR 200 sms. Minute are the base which are called units. On the given limits for SMS and units (minutes) the exchange ratio will be calculated. Costs are based on this ratio, you input only unit costs if you want the costs feature. Enabling this will disable individual sms-only and calltime-only limits.</string>
    <string name="pref_units_free_sum">How many minutes you can talk. It is the base unit for that limit.</string>
    <string name="pref_units_free">Free minutes (units)</string>
    <string name="pref_units_sms_free_sum">OR how many SMS can spend in a month.</string>
    <string name="pref_units_sms_free">Free SMS</string>
    <string name="pref_costs_limit">Costs Limit</string>
    <string name="pref_costs_limit_sum">Activate if you have a (personal) cost limit which you want to monitor. If this is activated DroidStats manages the overview boxes not showing more than 3.</string>
    <string name="pref_costs_free_sum">The maximum amount you want to spend and on which you want to get warned when you reach it.</string>
    <string name="pref_costs_free">Costlimit amount</string>
    <string name="costs_remaining">Costs remaining</string>
    <string name="estimated_costs">Estimated costs</string>
    <string name="units_remaining">Units remaining</string>
    <string name="estimated_units">Estimated units</string>
    <string name="applist_textbox_search">Search App</string>
    <string name="pref_showunits">Show units</string>
    <string name="widgetconfig_4slot">4. Slot</string>
    <string name="widgetconfig_3slot">3. Slot</string>
    <string name="widgetconfig_2slot">2. Slot</string>
    <string name="widgetconfig_1slot">1. Slot</string>
    <string name="widgetconfig_configure">Configure</string>
    <string name="button_search">Search</string>
    <string name="applist_system_apps">System Apps</string>
    <string name="applist_downloaded_apps">Downloaded Apps</string>
    <string name="data_per_app_shortcuttitle">Data per App</string>
    <string name="data_per_app_button">Data per App</string>
    <string name="applist_not_supported_text">Sadly this feature is not supported by your handset or your custom ROM.</string>
    <string name="applist_feature_not_supported">Feature Not Supported</string>
    <string name="dataperapp_info_text">"Data amount listed is the data usage since the last boot of your phone. Data usage is across all interfaces of the phone. This includes wifi, 3G, usb and bluetooth for example. Android system doesn't provide splitted data."</string>
    <string name="applist_getting_data">Getting data</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_1x1_oneslot_unitsadded_sum">Only affects One Slot widget</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_statusbarwidget_sum">A widget that integrates in the notification area.</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_use_statusbarwidget">Use Status Bar Widget</string>
    <string name="widget_config_title">Widget Info</string>
    <string name="widgetconfig_premium_support4x1">The 4x1 widget is part of our features for donators. Help us and support us to make DroidStats even better. Many other features will get unlocked too. Android Market Donation unlocks also possibility to configure all widgets and more.</string>
    <string name="widgetconfig_premium_supportedconfig">Configuring the widgets is part of our features for donators. You can re-order the values and set upcounting values for example. Help us and support us to make DroidStats even better. Many other features will get unlocked too.</string>
    <string name="widgetconfig_premium">Support us</string>
    <string name="widgetconfig_back">Back</string>
    <string name="pref_use1SlotWidget">Use as One-Slot Widget</string>
    <string name="pref_use1SlotWidget_sum">Widget which looks like the bigger widgets and can display limit bars.</string>
    <string name="pref_status_bar_widget">Status Bar Widget</string>
    <string name="pref_status_bar_widget_theme">Widget Theme</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_4x1">Widget 4x1</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_3x1">Widget 3x1</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_2x1">Widget 2x1</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_1x1">Widget 1x1</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_other">Other</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_values">Values</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_transparency">Transparency</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_transparency_sum">Pre Froyo phones can only use certain levels of transparency.</string>
    <string name="average_outgoing_paid_calls_length">Average Outgoing Paid Calls Length</string>
    <string name="average_outgoing_paid_sms_length">Average Outgoing Paid SMS Length</string>
    <string name="average_outgoing_paid_calls_length_sum">How long your calls are in average. It analyses calls which you have to pay for and which are outgoing.</string>
    <string name="average_outgoing_paid_sms_length_sum">How many characters your SMS contain in average. Analyses outgoing SMS to numbers you have to pay for.</string>
    <string name="pref_useHoursDisplay">Prefer Hours/Minute format</string>
    <string name="pref_useHoursDisplay_sum">Replaces for example 130 min to 2 h 10 min in the detailed stats</string>
    <string name="about_title">About &amp; Infos</string>
    <string name="about_facebook">Facebook Group</string>
    <string name="about_donation_market">Donation Market (Premium)</string>
    <string name="about_donation_paypal">Donation Paypal</string>
    <string name="about_upgrade">Upgrade (Support Us)</string>
    <string name="about_homepage">Homepage</string>
    <string name="premium_invalid_title">Key problem</string>
    <string name="premium_invalid_alert">Could not validate key. Maybe the google licensing server had problems (offline? please restart). Licensing data is checked periodically online. Contact us if you consider problems.</string>
    <string name="pref_manual_corr_numlabel">Correction Contact</string>
    <string name="manual_corr_calls">minutes (out)</string>
    <string name="manual_corr_sms">SMS (out)</string>
    <string name="manual_corr_traffic">mb data (out)</string>
    <string name="pref_manual_corr_add">Add ...</string>
    <string name="pref_manual_corr_hint">... to your current data. Date for correction is today.</string>
    <string name="pref_upateIntervallSMS">Update Interval SMS</string>
    <string name="pref_upateIntervallSMS_sum">"How often DroidStats should check sent and received sms messages. If you don't send much messages raise that value. More calculations needed as for data usage counting. If background services are disabled it only will be checked on application startup."</string>
    <string name="pref_upateIntervallTraffic">Update Interval Data Usage</string>
    <string name="pref_upateIntervallTraffic_sum">How often DroidStats should check interface infos for data usage tracking (affects accuracy)</string>
    <string name="pref_actions">Actions</string>
    <string name="pref_actions_sum">One-time actions like reset the database or do a manual correction</string>
    <string name="pref_manual_correction">Manual Data Correction</string>
    <string name="pref_manual_correction_sum">Are in the middle of the month or upgraded your phone? Maybe you want to set a start amount for your usage. This is NOT for raising your monthly limit.</string>
    <string name="quickaction_stat_info">Stat info</string>
    <string name="favorite_toggle_add">Add to favorites</string>
    <string name="favorite_toogle_remove">Remove from favorites</string>
    <string name="pref_billIncomingCalls">Bill incoming calls</string>
    <string name="pref_billIncomingSMS">Bill incoming SMS</string>
    <string name="pref_billIncomingCalls_sum">If your incoming calls are billed too check this option. If enabled excluded times, numbers and costs are used for incoming calls too</string>
    <string name="pref_billIncomingSMS_sum">If your incoming sms are billed too check this option. If enabled excluded numbers and costs are used for incoming sms too</string>
    <string name="excludedtimes_quickinfo">"Add days and times where you can call for free. If you have the situation that you can have free calls on weekends, you add a filter for Weekend from 12 AM to 12AM the next day. Maybe your weekend is a little bit wider, then you add for example Friday 7 PM to 12 AM(next day) and Monday from 12 AM to 5 AM. Don't overlap midnight, add 2 different limits."</string>
    <string name="excludedSMSNumbers_quickinfo">Add numbers and contacts you can text for free. Also you can add patterns which filter numbers which match this pattern. If you have free numbers using the * symbol you can enable in the options to choose @ as pattern symbol. To get better results please enable the Country Code Correction.</string>
    <string name="excludedCallnumbers_quickinfo">Add numbers and contacts you can call for free. Also you can add patterns which filter numbers which match this pattern. If you have free numbers using the * symbol you can enable in the options to choose @ as pattern symbol. To get better results please enable the Country Code Correction.</string>
    <string name="costsettings_quickinfo">If Cost-Feature is enabled costs get calculated. They will be shown in the overview. If you have limits enabled cost only get calculated if you are over the limits. Also connection fees are not calculated if you use calltime limits.</string>
    <string name="widgetconfg_remainingdata">Remaining Data this period</string>
    <string name="widgetconfig_remainingsms">Remaining SMS this period</string>
    <string name="widgetconfig_remainingcalltime">Remaining Calltime this period</string>
    <string name="widgetconfig_configdesc">Data displayed on the Widget:</string>
    <string name="widgetconfig_addwidget">Add Widget</string>
    <string name="average_monthly_outgoing_payed_minutes">Average Outgoing paid minutes (Month)</string>
    <string name="average_weekly_outgoing_payed_minutes">Average Outgoing paid minutes (Week)</string>
    <string name="average_monthly_sms_sent">Average Outgoing SMS (Month)</string>
    <string name="average_weekly_sms_sent">Average Outgoing SMS (Week)</string>
    <string name="descriptionAverageMonthlySmsSent">How many SMS you send in average each month</string>
    <string name="descriptionAverageWeeklySmsSent">How many SMS you send in average each week</string>
    <string name="descriptionAverageMonthlyOutgoingPayedMinutes">How many minutes you get billed in average each month</string>
    <string name="descriptionAverageWeeklyOutgoingPayedMinutes">How many minutes you get billed in average each week</string>
    <string name="pref_ccc_title">Country Code Correction</string>
    <string name="pref_ccc_sum">Adds your country code to numbers without country code for better stats. Especially if you use free numbers feature this is important.</string>
    <string name="pref_ccc_useCCC">add country code on numbers without country code (affects DS only)</string>
    <string name="pref_ccc_countrycode">Your country code (without leading plus)</string>
    <string name="pref_ccc_transformations"><u>Example Number Transformations:</u></string>
    <string name="sync_progress_correction">Correcting numbers</string>
    <string name="pref_forceEnglish">Force English Language</string>
    <string name="pref_forceEnglish_sum">If you have DroidStats in another language you can choose this option to use it in English</string>
    <string name="pref_excludetimes_dialog_title">Select weekday and hours</string>
    <string name="pref_excludelist_dialog_addtime">Add time</string>
    <string name="pref_excludetime_timeinfo">Set the starthour and endhour of your free time.</string>
    <string name="pref_free_times">Days and hours - Filter</string>
    <string name="pref_free_times_sum">"Exclude times and days in which your minutes aren't billed (ATM the calls have to begin in this period the be excluded)"</string>
    <string name="pref_excludelist_wildcard">You can use %1$s as a wildcard</string>
    <string name="pref_excludelist_alreadyin">number already in</string>
    <string name="pref_excludelist_patternmatches">Your pattern matches %1$s numbers</string>
    <string name="pref_excludelist_number">Number:</string>
    <string name="pref_excludelist_name">Name:</string>
    <string name="pref_excludelist_unknown">[unknown]</string>
    <string name="general">General</string>
    <string name="button_continue_import">Continue &amp; Import</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_welcome">Welcome to DroidStats</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_whats_new">"What's new?"</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">" Thanks for installing DroidStats.

 To use DroidStats you should configure how much "<b>free minutes, free sms and free data</b>" is included with your plan. If you don't have limits you can set your "<b>personal limits</b>" to save costs. If you reach limits you will get notified and the progress bars gets colored orange and red.

 There are four different tabs, the first tab is the overview, which provides you with compact information about the current month. The other tabs give you detailed information about every service (Calls, SMS, Data). You can click on each statistic in that lists to get more informations. In the calls and SMS view you can click on the contact photos in the top lists to use "<b>QuickActions</b>".

 For a better and faster control over your month, try the widgets. There are 3 different widgets, the biggest one of them also shows you your data limit.

 Please don't forget to adjust your "<b>billing increment</b> to that of your provider. You can also set the <b>first day of the month</b> when your bill starts. This app <b>emulates the behaviour</b>" of your provider, but it isn't possible to adjust to all kinds of plans. It is not possible to determine to what provider you are calling. This data has ONLY your provider. If you have "<b>free numbers you can exclude</b>" them in the options.

 DroidStats syncs your SMS in/outbox and your call log with an own event log. Don't care about the Androids internal 500 calls limit and about deleted SMS and calls, they will be counted also after DroidStats is installed to improve the quality of the counters. There is no warranty on the calculated data.s

 If you own a "<b>slower device</b> like a HTC Dream, HTC Magic or HTC Hero please disable the animations in the options of DroidStats to fasten up the app. Please <b>"don't use Task Killers"</b>" to kill DroidStats.

 Bear in mind that the first month of measuring starts with installing this app.

 You can find my email address in the about and contact me if you have questions or find bugs

 Have Fun "</string>
    <string name="descriptionTodayMobile">Shows the amount of sent and received data traffic with your mobile internet interface (2G/3G) from today.</string>
    <string name="descriptionMonthMobile">Shows the amount of sent and received data traffic with your mobile internet interface (2G/3G) from this billing month. Tracking of traffic begins with the installation of the app.</string>
    <string name="descriptionTotalMobile">Shows the amount of sent and received data traffic with your mobile internet interface (2G/3G) alltime.</string>
    <string name="descriptionTodayWifi">Shows the amount of sent and received data traffic with your wifi interface (Wireless LAN) from today.</string>
    <string name="descriptionMonthWifi">Shows the amount of sent and received data traffic with your wifi interface (Wireless LAN) from this billing month..</string>
    <string name="descriptionTotalWifi">Shows the amount of sent and received data traffic with your wifi interface (Wireless LAN) alltime.</string>
    <string name="data">Data</string>
    <string name="data_tab">Data</string>
    <string name="price_per_mb_data">price per MB data</string>
    <string name="use_cost_option_data">enable data costs</string>
    <string name="interface_not_discovered_yet">Interface not discovered yet</string>
    <string name="button_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="button_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="sure">Sure?</string>
    <string name="pref_reset_standart_check">reset call/sms counters</string>
    <string name="pref_reset_data_check">reset data counters</string>
    <string name="pref_reset_interfaces_check">rediscover interfaces</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="pref_reset_dialog">"Are you sure you want to reset? The data will be recreated from the phones call log and the sms messages in your inbox / outbox. Everything you have deleted there can not be considered when recreating the statistics. The data for data counters is recollected from interface counters over time. If you have severe problems with data usage counting also check 'rediscover interfaces'."</string>
    <string name="data_remaining">Data remaining</string>
    <string name="estimated_data">Estimated data</string>
    <string name="pref_traffic_free_sum">The amount of data traffic you can use every month</string>
    <string name="pref_traffic_free">Free Data</string>
    <string name="pref_traffic_limit_sum">Activate if you have included free (internet) data in your contract.</string>
    <string name="pref_traffic_limit">Data Limit</string>
    <string name="traffic_daily">Today</string>
    <string name="traffic_monthly">Month</string>
    <string name="traffic_alltime">Total</string>
    <string name="infoLimits">"Please configure the limits in the settings and read the info's in the About dialog. If you don't want to use limits you can enable the cost settings solely.
 
You can use swipe gestures to pan between the screens."</string>
    <string name="costs">Costs</string>
    <string name="pref_alternativepattern_sum">"Since some providers use '*' as a symbol in their numbers, using @ is an alternative"</string>
    <string name="pref_alternativepattern">Use @ as exclude-pattern symbol</string>
    <string name="title">Nitro DroidStats</string>
    <string name="sms_tab">SMS</string>
    <string name="calls_tab">Calls</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="unit_overview">Units:</string>
    <string name="costs_overview">Costs:</string>
    <string name="calls_overview">Calls:</string>
    <string name="sms_overview">SMS:</string>
    <string name="data_overview">Mobile Data:</string>
    <string name="add">add</string>
    <string name="total">Total</string>
    <string name="monthly">Monthly</string>
    <string name="mobile">Mobile</string>
    <string name="wifi">Wifi</string>
    <string name="estimated_good">(Good)</string>
    <string name="estimated_bad">(Bad)</string>
    <string name="remaining_days_label">remaining days of billing month</string>
    <string name="estimated_sms">Estimated SMS</string>
    <string name="estimated_minutes">Estimated minutes</string>
    <string name="sms_remaining">SMS remaining</string>
    <string name="minutes_remaining">Minutes remaining</string>
    <string name="extra_costs">Extra costs</string>
    <string name="descriptionIncomingSmsMonthly">The number of SMS you have received this month</string>
    <string name="descriptionOutgoingSmsMonthly">The number of SMS you have sent this month</string>
    <string name="descriptionIncomingSms">The number of SMS you have ever received</string>
    <string name="descriptionOutgoingSms">The number of SMS you have ever sent</string>
    <string name="descriptionIncomingSMSPaidMonthly">The number of SMS you have received this month excluding your free numbers and including multiple sms (sms splitting)</string>
    <string name="descriptionOutgoingSMSPaidMonthly">The number of SMS you have sent this month excluding your free numbers and including multiple sms (sms splitting)</string>
    <string name="descriptionIncomingSMSPaid">The number of SMS you have ever received excluding your free numbers and including multiple sms (sms splitting)</string>
    <string name="descriptionOutgoingSMSPaid">The number of SMS you have ever sent excluding your free numbers and including multiple sms (sms splitting)</string>
    <string name="incoming_sms">Incoming SMS</string>
    <string name="outgoing_sms">Outgoing SMS</string>
    <string name="incoming_sms_paid">Incoming Paid SMS</string>
    <string name="outgoing_sms_paid">Outgoing Paid SMS</string>
    <string name="descriptionMissedCallsMonthly">"The number of calls you have missed (you didn't answer) this month."</string>
    <string name="descriptionIncomingCallsMonthly">The number of incoming calls you received this month.</string>
    <string name="descriptionIncomingMinutesMonthly">The amount of minutes by incoming calls in this month.</string>
    <string name="descriptionFailedCallsMonthly">The number of calls no person answered this month. Excluding things like mailboxes which cost money.</string>
    <string name="descriptionOutgoingCallsMonthly">The number of outgoing calls you did this month</string>
    <string name="descriptionOutgoingPayedMinutesMonthly">The number of minutes that you will have to pay for this month for outgoing calls. Excluded numbers are excluded. Note: This may be higher than the actually outgoing minutes depending on your contracts billing increment(e.g. 1/1, 10/60, 60/60) or lower with many excluded numbers</string>
    <string name="descriptionOutgoingMinutesMonthly">The actual amout of minutes you spend calling this month.</string>
    <string name="descriptionFailedCallsTotal">The total number of calls no person answered. Excluding things like mailboxes which cost money.</string>
    <string name="descriptionOutgoingCallsTotal">The total number of outgoing calls you ever did.</string>
    <string name="descriptionMissedCallsTotal">"The total number of calls you have missed (you didn't answer)."</string>
    <string name="descriptionIncomingCallsTotal">The total number of incoming calls you ever received.</string>
    <string name="descriptionIncomingMinutesTotal">The total minutes you spend with incoming calls.</string>
    <string name="descriptionOutgoingPayedMinutesTotal">The total amount of minutes that you had / have to pay for outgoing calls. Excluded numbers are excluded. Note: This may be higher than the actually outgoing minutes depending on your contracts billing increment(e.g. 1/1, 10/60, 60/60)</string>
    <string name="descriptionOutgoingMinutesTotal">The total amount of outgoing minutes you actually spend calling.</string>
    <string name="descriptionIncomingPayedMinutesTotal">The total amount of minutes that you had / have to pay for incoming calls. Excluded numbers are excluded. Note: This may be higher than the actually incoming minutes depending on your contracts billing increment(e.g. 1/1, 10/60, 60/60)</string>
    <string name="descriptionIncomingPayedMinutesMonth">The number of minutes that you will have to pay for this month for incoming calls. Excluded numbers are excluded. Note: This may be higher than the actually incoming minutes depending on your contracts billing increment(e.g. 1/1, 10/60, 60/60) or lower with many excluded numbers</string>
    <string name="descriptionOutgoingMinutesPayed">The total amount of minutes that you have to paid for. Note: This may be higher than the actually outgoing minutes depending on your contracts billing (e.g. 1/1, 10/60, 60/60)</string>
    <string name="descriptionOutgoingMinutes">The total amount of minutes you spend calling.</string>
    <string name="missed_calls">Missed calls</string>
    <string name="incoming_calls">Incoming calls</string>
    <string name="incoming_paid_calls">Incoming paid calls</string>
    <string name="incoming_minutes">Incoming minutes</string>
    <string name="incoming_payed_minutes">Incoming paid minutes</string>
    <string name="failed_calls">Failed calls</string>
    <string name="outgoing_calls">Outgoing calls</string>
    <string name="outgoing_paid_calls">Outgoing paid calls</string>
    <string name="outgoing_payed_minutes">Outgoing paid minutes</string>
    <string name="outgoing_minutes">Outgoing minutes</string>
    <string name="sync_progress_2">Analyze events</string>
    <string name="sync_progress_1">Sync from system</string>
    <string name="progress_working">Working..</string>
    <string name="starting_sync">Starting Sync</string>
    <string name="first_sync_message">"Sync Data (The first sync can take some minutes.)

Checkout the nice widgets after the sync."</string>
    <string name="unit_calls">calls</string>
    <string name="unit_minutes">min</string>
    <string name="unit_seconds">sec</string>
    <string name="unit_sms">sms</string>
    <string name="unit_sms_chars">chars</string>
    <string name="unit_units">units</string>
    <string name="app_name">DroidStats</string>
    <string name="event_log_phone">phone</string>
    <string name="event_log_call_time">call time</string>
    <string name="event_log_billed_time">billed time</string>
    <string name="event_log_message_length">message length</string>
    <string name="event_log_billed_messages">billed messages</string>
    <string name="event_log_homescreen_shortcut">Event log</string>
    <string name="event_log_filtering">filtering...</string>
    <string name="stat_list_mode_favorites">Show Favorites</string>
    <string name="stat_list_mode_all">Show All</string>
    <string name="calltime_limit_invalid">Call time Limit not set valid</string>
    <string name="sms_limit_invalid">SMS Limit not set valid</string>
    <string name="unit_limit_invalid">Unit Limit (minutes) not set valid</string>
    <string name="unit_sms_limit_invalid">Unit Limit (sms) not set valid</string>
    <string name="warning_treshold_invalid">Warning threshold not set valid</string>
    <string name="costs_limit_invalid">Cost Limit not set valid</string>
    <string name="menu_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="menu_help">About &amp; Help</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_log">Event Log</string>
    <string name="menu_import_export">Import/Export</string>
    <string name="menu_csv_export">Export CSV</string>
    <string name="menu_upgrade">Upgrade</string>
    <string name="about">" "<b>Nitro DroidStats</b>" 

developed by "<b>Michael Ludwig</b>" 
GUI and support by "<b>David Eberlein</b>" 

 If you like this app, please consider a "<b>upgrade/donation</b>". See the links below. Upgrade unlocks a lot of extra features. 

 For "<b>updates</b>" please have a look at the market

 "<b>Help &amp; more:</b>" 

 "<ul> <li>This application has different widgets to help you stay in your limits. Go ahead and try them.</li>" 

 "<li>You can touch every item in the stats to show the top 3</li>" 

 "<li>The thumbs in the overview indicate wether you will be over your limit till the end of the month or not if you continue your usage as before.</li>" 

 "<li>Datatraffic counting begins with the installation of the app and gets more representative after a while.</li>" 

 "<li>Froyo-way Apps2SD is not possible with apps containing background services and widgets.</li>" 

 "<li>If you use an application like <b>AndroidAIR Mail</b> or <b>WebSMS</b>" you could have extra SMS's in your outbox which will be counted with this application but not paid through your bill. Pay attention. "</li>" 

 "<li>If you find <b>bugs</b> please email me (mail.michael.ludwig@gmail.com) or visit the UserVoice on our homepage </li>" 

 "<li>To get more informations visit our facebook group or homepage</li>" 
 "</ul>" "</string>
    <string name="limitsInvalid">Warning: threshold or limits not set valid</string>
    <string name="notify_smsLimitReached">SMS limit exceeded</string>
    <string name="notify_smsLimitNear">SMS limit is near</string>
    <string name="notify_limitNear">Limit is near</string>
    <string name="notify_limitExceeded">Limit exceeded</string>
    <string name="notify_smsLimitNearBody">You are reaching your monthly SMS limit</string>
    <string name="notify_smsLimitReachedBody">You exceeded your monthly SMS limit</string>
    <string name="notify_callLimitReachedBody">You exceeded your monthly free minute limit</string>
    <string name="notify_callLimitNearBody">You are reaching your monthly free minute limit</string>
    <string name="notify_callLimitNear">Free minute limit is near</string>
    <string name="notify_callLimitReached">Free minute limit exceeded</string>
    <string name="notify_costsLimitReachedBody">You exceeded your monthly costs limit</string>
    <string name="notify_costsLimitNearBody">You are reaching your monthly costs limit</string>
    <string name="notify_costsLimitNear">Costs limit is near</string>
    <string name="notify_costsLimitReached">Costs limit exceeded</string>
    <string name="notify_unitsLimitReachedBody">You exceeded your monthly unit limit</string>
    <string name="notify_unitsLimitNearBody">You are reaching your monthly unit limit</string>
    <string name="notify_unitsLimitNear">Unit limit is near</string>
    <string name="notify_unitsLimitReached">Unit limit exceeded</string>
    <string name="button_close">Close</string>
    <string name="cron_picker_monthly_day_of_month_n">Day of Month: %1$s</string>
    <string name="contact_or_number">contact or number</string>
    <string name="save_and_return">save and return</string>
    <string name="price_per_message">price per message:</string>
    <string name="cents">cents</string>
    <string name="price_per_minute">price per minute:</string>
    <string name="price_per_unit">price per unit (minute):</string>
    <string name="use_cost_option">use cost option</string>
    <string name="use_call_cost_option">enable call costs</string>
    <string name="use_sms_cost_option">enable sms costs</string>
    <string name="use_unit_cost_option">enable units costs</string>
    <string name="cost_settings">Cost settings</string>
    <string name="pref_limits">Monthly Limits</string>
    <string name="pref_limits_sum">Configure the monthly limits of your contract</string>
    <string name="pref_calltime_limit">Call Time Limit</string>
    <string name="pref_calltime_limit_sum">Activate if you have free minutes in your contract</string>
    <string name="pref_calltime_free">Free Minutes</string>
    <string name="pref_calltime_free_sum">The amount of minutes that are free for you</string>
    <string name="pref_sms_limit">SMS Limit</string>
    <string name="pref_sms_limit_sum">Activate if you have free sms in your contract</string>
    <string name="pref_sms_free">Free SMS</string>
    <string name="pref_sms_free_sum">The amount of sms that are free for you</string>
    <string name="pref_month_beginning">Billing Month Beginning</string>
    <string name="pref_month_beginning_sum">The day your carrier does your monthly billing, e.g. 1</string>
    <string name="pref_billing">Billing</string>
    <string name="pref_billing_sum">Settings for costs, billing, number and time exceptions</string>
    <string name="pref_costs">Cost Settings</string>
    <string name="pref_costs_sum">Set sms, call and data pricing</string>
    <string name="pref_billing_increment">Billing Increment</string>
    <string name="pref_billing_increment_sum">Your contracts billing increment (first period/following periods) in seconds</string>
    <string name="pref_free_call_num">Free Numbers (Calls)</string>
    <string name="pref_free_call_num_sum">Set the numbers you can call for free</string>
    <string name="pref_free_sms_num">Free Numbers (SMS)</string>
    <string name="pref_free_sms_num_sum">Set the numbers you can text free</string>
    <string name="pref_split_sms">Count Long SMS Split</string>
    <string name="pref_split_sms_sum">Count SMS longer 160 chars splitted (Multiple SMS)</string>
    <string name="pref_app">Application Settings</string>
    <string name="pref_app_sum">Settings regarding the Applications</string>
    <string name="pref_estimations">Monthly Usage Estimations</string>
    <string name="pref_estimations_sum">Show estimations for the monthly sms and minutes based on previous days (after one week of billing month)</string>
    <string name="pref_call_notification">Send Call Notifications</string>
    <string name="pref_call_notification_sum">Select to receive status bar notifications when approaching and exceeding your call limit</string>
    <string name="pref_sms_notification">Send SMS Notifications</string>
    <string name="pref_sms_notification_sum">Select to receive status bar notifications when approaching and exceeding your sms limit</string>
    <string name="pref_traffic_notification">Send Data Notifications</string>
    <string name="pref_traffic_notification_sum">Select to receive status bar notifications when approaching and exceeding your data limit</string>
    <string name="pref_unit_notification">Send Unit Notifications</string>
    <string name="pref_unit_notification_sum">Select to receive status bar notifications when approaching and exceeding your units limit</string>
    <string name="pref_costs_notification">Send Costs Notifications</string>
    <string name="pref_costs_notification_sum">Select to receive status bar notifications when approaching and exceeding your costs limit</string>
    <string name="pref_threshold">Warning Threshold</string>
    <string name="pref_threshold_sum">Threshold in percent (%) of when to warn you of reaching your limits. Indicated through notifications (if enabled) and the color of the bars.</string>
    <string name="pref_advanced">Advanced Settings</string>
    <string name="pref_services">Enable Background Services</string>
    <string name="pref_services_sum">"May be disabled to save battery if widgets and notifications aren't used. Also background sms polling won't be done."</string>
    <string name="pref_animaions_off">Disable Animations</string>
    <string name="pref_animaions_off_sum">Makes the app faster on slow devices. (restarts app)</string>
    <string name="pref_reset_db">Reset Database</string>
    <string name="pref_reset_db_sum">Resets the database and rebuilds it out of the call log and sms inbox</string>
    <string name="pref_reset_db_dialog">"Are you sure you want to reset the database?

The data will be recreated from the call log and sms inbox."</string>
    <string name="provider_interface_alias_wifi">Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="provider_interface_alias_3g">2G/3G Network</string>
    <string name="provider_interface_alias_ethernet">Ethernet</string>
    <string name="provider_interface_alias_loopback">Loopback</string>
    <string name="notification_usage_level_medium_title">Medium usage level reached</string>
    <string name="notification_usage_level_medium">The mobile data interface (2G/3G) has reached medium usage</string>
    <string name="notification_usage_level_high_title">High usage level reached</string>
    <string name="notification_usage_level_high">The mobile data interface (2G/3G) has reached high usage</string>
    <string name="pref_widget">Widget Settings</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_sum">Customize your widgets</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_micro_stat1">Choose First Stat</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_micro_stat1_sum">The first (upper) stat displayed on the widget</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_micro_stat2">Choose Second Stat</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_micro_stat2_sum">The second (lower) stat displayed on the widget</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_micro_stat3">Choose Third Stat</string>
    <string name="pref_widget_micro_stat4">Choose Forth Stat</string>
    <string name="resetdate_not_available">not available</string>
    <string name="resetdate_since">since</string>
    <string name="about_share_app">Share App</string>
    <string name="app_share_subject">App Recommandation: DroidStats</string>
    <string name="app_share_text">Hey, I want to recommend an app to you. It is called DroidStats and is very useful. Download it here: http://bit.ly/DroidStats-GooglePlay It also has an extended Premium version!</string>
    <string name="app_share_chooser">How do you want to share?</string>
</resources>
